911fonts.com 2019-03-21

# Help | Privacy Policy www.911fonts.com - Fonts archive with more than 40 000+ fonts. Zephyr font, Gill sans, Bembo font, cyrillic font download, graffity fonts, fonts.

**Third Party Advertising:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

 **Third Party Cookies:**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

 **Personal Information:**

This Web site requests non-obligatory personal information from our members. The only required information is your name and e-mail adress. We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes, including  selling. You are under no obligation to give your real name when submitting a tab or when becoming a member.

 **External Links:**

This site contains links to other sites. 911fonts.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, or their content.

 **Security:**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

 **Contacting the Web Site:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact -  admin[at]911fonts.com. 

**Date** : 2010-01-08

**Author** : admin
